Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 9. Water Irrigation files
  - Subseries 1. Boulder Dam
    - Correspondence, blueprints, clippings, legal briefs re: All American Canal contract, Colorado River Dam fund, Malewind Will case, and the Packer Dam contract, 1931 - 1933, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence from Herbert V. Clotts, Assistant Director of Irrigation, 1931, Steart & Shaw to Ed F. Williams, 1931, Northcutt Ely to Thomas C. Yeager, memoranda between Childers (Imperial Valley Irrigation District) & Yeager (Coachella Valley County Water District) & Ely, 1970 Nov. 24, Sen. Henry F. Ashhurst, 1933, Carl Haydn, 1933, Judge Dent, 1933, Richard J. Coffey, 1933, H.N. Savage, 1933; draft of California Division of Water Rights; clippings on Boulder Dam; and legal briefs re: Charles Malan vs. Imperial Dam, et al., Superior Court, Imperial Co., 1933.
    - Clippings, correspondence, reports1930 - 1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence from Northcutt Ely and Ray Lyman Wilbur.
    - Reports, correspondence1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      Includes reports and correspondence re: All American Canal, Upper Gila River, Boulder Dam. Correspondents include: Northcutt Ely; Stewart, Shaw, & Murray; George A. Hastings (Administrative Asst. to the President)
    - Correspondence, reports, clippings, memos re: SB 40391931 - 1940, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      Includes contract for delivery of Arizona water; report on "Hydrology"; material relating to Colorado River, Boulder Dam, Arizona water controversy; correspondence between Sims, Ely, Ickes.
    - Arizona water contract1930 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      Correspondence; reports; memos from Ely to Rep. L.W. Douglas, E.B. Deblen, F.E. Weymouth, and R.J. Coffey; and drafts of contract
    - BCPA Congressional record re: Colorado River, Accession no. M0269; photostats (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Clippings re: Boulder Dam, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Telegram, correspondence, and memos1931 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 8)
      Includes correspondence from Ray Lyman Wilbur, Edward Hyatt (State Engineer). Topics include HR 4715 Palo Verde Valley and Colorado River
  - Subseries 2. Hoover Dam
    - Hoover Dam - Imperial Irrigation District1930 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence, reports, memors, telegrams, statistics, and maps re: the All American canal. Correspondents include E.K. Burlew, Ely, Wilbur, W.A. Jump (budget officer), Weymouth, Matthews, W.P. Whitsett, D.E. Carpenter, Walker Young, E. Mead, D.E. Carpenter, Coffey
    - Arizona water - Colorado River1932 - 1933, Accession no. M0269 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      Includes memos, correspondence, telegrams, and contract draft, notes. Correspondents include Ely, Wilbur, E. Mead, E.B. Debler (Chief engineer, Denver), B.B. Moeur (Gov., Arizona), Coffey, Dent
    - Coachella1931 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 11)
      Correspondence between Ely and Wilbur, memo, report.
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - construction1930 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 12)
      Correspondence; memoranda; contracts; chronology; South Sierras Construction pwr contract, blueprint. Correspondents include Dent; H.P. Fabian; T.R. Walther; E.K. Burlew; W.R. Vallance (Bar Assoc.); Mead
    - Hoover Dam - miscellaneous1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 13)
      Correspondence; memoranda; speech notes; pamphlets; statistics. Correspondents include George W. Malone; Ely; T.R. Walther; Joseph Finemore; Virgil A. Martin; K.F. Walter; Mead
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - correspondence1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 14)
      telegrams from W.C. Mullendore, W.B. Matthews, Mead, Wilbur, and Weymouth.
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - correspondence1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 15)
      telegrams correspondence, reports, memos, graph, photostats of Ray Lyman Wilbur articles. Correspondents include Wilbur, Dent, Helen True (Secretary to President), C.P. Squires, P.D. Swing, Mead, L.W. Bannister, E.F. Scattergood, Matthews, Whisett, Finney (solicitor).
    - Colorado River - litigation, briefs1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 16)
      Whitsett; Finney; Hoover; Wilbur; Ely
    - Hoover Dam - municipalities (general)1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 111, Folder 17)
      correspondence, contract, memoranda with Dent and Coffey.
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - municipalities1930 - 1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 18)
      correspondence, statistics, contract drafts, reports. Correspondents include J.W. Charleville (City Engineer, Glendale, Calif.); Finney; Coffey; Wilbur; Swing; Joseph M. Dixon (Acting Secretary of the Interior).
    - Hoover Dam - confidential1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 19)
      correspondence, statistics, contract drafts, reports. Correspondents include Swing, Ely, Matthews.
    - Hoover Dam - Arizona suit1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 20)
      printed case - State of Arizona vs. State of California, et al., Supreme Court, 1930 Oct.
    - Hoover Dam - correspondence with the press1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 21)
      New York Times; Santa Ana Times
    - Hoover Dam - financial operation1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 22)
      memos; statistics; notes; photostats
    - Hoover Dam - press releasesca. 1930 - 1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Hoover Dam - appropriation hearings (House)1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 24)
      correspondence, reports, memoranda
    - Hoover Dam - roads1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 25)
      maps, memo re: road from Kingman to Hoover Dam
    - Hoover Dam - dedication1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 26)
      correspondence from Sen. Pittman, Lawrence Rickey (Secretary to the President); articles
    - Hoover Dam - legal memos1929, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Hoover Dam - Boulder Canyon Project Act: HR 57731928, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Hoover Dam - steam - electric costs1925 - 1929, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 29)
      statistics
    - Boulder Dam - press releases1924 - 1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Hoover Dam - finances1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 112, Folder 31)
      memos, graphs, financial statements
    - Hoover Dam - power regulations1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 113, Folder 32)
      contracts, correspondence between Wilbur and Ely
    - The electric power requirements of the State of California and the value of by-product electric power ....: report / by James E. McCaffrey & E.W. Kramer,1930, Accession no. M0269; 1 binder (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - S.B. 728 Boulder Canyon Project1928, Accession no. M0269; 1 binder (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Boulder Dam hearing: Allocation of power to be generated, 1929, Accession no. M0269 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Hoover Dam - L.A. general1931 - 1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 113, Folder 36)
      correspondence, memoranda, reports. Correspondents include Ely; Baxter & Carpenter; J.H. Howard (Los Angeles Municipal Water District); Louis C. Cranston; E.J. Scattergood; R.R. Lamont.
    - Hoover Dam - power companies, Accession no. M0269 (Box 113, Folder 37)
      memoranda
    - Hoover Dam - power companies, Accession no. M0269 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - Hoover Dam - Metropolitan Water District, Accession no. M0269 (Box 114, Folder 38)
      telegrams, correspondence, memoranda. Correspondents include D.T. Johnson, Jr.; Paul E. Schwab; Weymouth; E.J. Scattergood; S.C. Evans; Mathews; Whitsett; R.L. Criswell; Louis C. Hill, engineer
    - Hoover Dam - Metropolitan Water District, Accession no. M0269 (Box 115, Folder 39)
      clippings, correspondence, resolutions, S.B. 4755. Correspondents include S.C. Evans
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - State (Arizona & New Mexico)1929 - 1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 115, Folder 40)
      memos, correspondence, statistics
    - Hoover Dam - City of Los Angeles1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 116, Folder 41)
      correspondence with Dixon, W. Turney Fox, H.A. Van Norman, Scattergood, Coffey
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - Los Angeles memos1929, Accession no. M0269 (Box 116, Folder 42)
    - Hoover Dam - New Mexico1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 117, Folder 43)
      correspondence between Ely and Wilbur
    - Hoover Dam - regulations1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 117, Folder 44)
      contracts, memos, regulations
    - Hoover Dam - statutes1928, Accession no. M0269 (Box 118, Folder 45)
      printed materials on Boulder Dam project
    - Colorado River litigation: memos Imperial Irrigation District, legal study, Accession no. M0269 (Box 119, Folder 46)
    - Colorado River litigation: correspondence with Childers, Thomas D.Thatcher, Accession no. M0269 (Box 119, Folder 47)
    - Hoover Dam - Advancement Association1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 120, Folder 48)
    - Hoover Dam - Justice1929 - 1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 120, Folder 49)
      memoranda to S.W. Richardson (Assistant Attorney General); Robert P. Reeder: William D. Mitchell (Attorney General).
    - Hoover Dam - Boulder City1930 - 1931, Accession no. M0269 (Box 120, Folder 50)
      Correspondence with Elizabeth Rowe; J.R. Alexander; Cranston; Finney; Coffey; Mead; Mathews.
    - Statement of audit to Bureau of Power & Light, Los Angeles / prepared by Price, Waterhouse, & Co., 1929 June 30, Accession no. M0269 (Box 121, Folder 51)
    - Hoover Dam - contracts - drafts1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 121, Folder 52)
    - Hoover Dam - allocations1929, Accession no. M0269 (Box 121, Folder 53)
      memoranda and reports
    - Hoover Dam - Mullendore1932, Accession no. M0269 (Box 122, Folder 54)
      correspondence
    - Hoover Dam - Six companies1932 Mar., Accession no. M0269 (Box 122, Folder 55)
      correspondence with Elwood Mead, James E. Watson & plaintiff's opening briefs in District Court of Nevada for Six Companies vs. A.J. Stinson, et al.
- Series 10. Colorado River files
  - Colorado River - navigability - maps, Accession no. M0269 (Box 123, Folder 56)
  - Colorado River - navigability: reports, 1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 123, Folder 57)
  - Colorado River - navigability: legal memos, Accession no. M0269 (Box 123, Folder 58)
  - Colorado River - litigation: memos by Ely1930, Accession no. M0269 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    Correspondents include Joseph W. Bingham (Stanford Law School); Dent; Robert P. Reeder (Dept. of Justice); Sol. Gen. Thomas D. Thacher; Dean Acheson
- Series 11. Water and mineral resources files
  - California State Water Plan, Accession no. M0365; 0304 (Box 74)
  - Carter & Schuler, Accession no. M0365; 0306 (Box 74)
  - Colorado River Literature, Accession no. M0365; 0341 (Box 74)
  - Colorado River Association (A-C), Accession no. M0365; 0342 (Box 74)
  - Colorado River Compact, Accession no. M0365; 0349 (Box 75)
  - Colorado River Program (A-Q), Accession no. M0365; 0350 (Box 75)
  - Colorado River Association (D-end), Accession no. M0365; 0342 (Box 124)
  - Colorado River Board - Six Agency, Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 125)
  - Colorado River Board (AO1-A06), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 126)
  - Small notebooks. "Master index by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 127)
  - Colorado River Board-A-1-1947-1949 etc., Accession no. M0365 (Box 128)
  - Colorado River Board-A-1-1947-1949 etc., Accession no. M0365 (Box 129)
  - Colorado River Board-A-1-1947-1949 etc., Accession no. M0365 (Box 130)
  - Colorado River Board-A-1-1947-1949 etc., Accession no. M0365 (Box 131)
  - Colorado River Board-A-1-1947-1949 etc., Accession no. M0365 (Box 132)
  - Pacific.Southwest Water Plan (series) Box 1 160z A 01-1602 B 07, Accession no. M0365 (Box 133)
  - Pacific.Southwest Water Plan (series) Box 1 160z A 01-1602 B 07, Accession no. M0365 (Box 134)
  - Pacific.Southwest Water Plan (series) Box 1 160z A 01-1602 B 07, Accession no. M0365 (Box 135)
  - Colorado River Board: contracts, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 136)
  - Colorado River Board: contracts, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 137)
  - Colorado River Board: contracts, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 138)
  - Colorado River Board: contracts, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 139)
  - Colorado River Board: contracts, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0344 (Box 140)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 141)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 142)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 143)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 144)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 145)
  - Colorado River Board, Accession no. M0365 (Box 146)
  - Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 147)
  - Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 148)
  - Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 149)
  - Speeches and Papers 01-61 (except 25-still current), Accession no. M0365; 1625 C (Box 150)
  - Speeches and Papers 01-61 (except 25-still current), Accession no. M0365; 1625 C (Box 151)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 152)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 153)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 154)
  - Colorado River Board: N. Crila Project, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 155)
  - Colorado River Board: N. Crila Project, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 156)
  - Colorado River Board: N. Crila Project, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 157)
  - Colorado River Board: N. Crila Project, etc., Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 158)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 159)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 160)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 161)
  - Mineral Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 162)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 163)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 164)
  - AV C (Arizona vs. California?), Accession no. M0365 (Box 165)
  - AV C (Arizona vs. California?), Accession no. M0365 (Box 166)
  - AV C (Arizona vs. California?), Accession no. M0365 (Box 167)
  - Water & Power, Accession no. M0365 (Box 168)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 169)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 170)
  - Misc. Water Resources Items + books for Stanford Library, Accession no. M0365 (Box 171)
  - Misc. Water Resources Items + books for Stanford Library, Accession no. M0365 (Box 172)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 173)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 174)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 175)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 176)
  - Arizona vs. California Water Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 177)
  - Arizona v. California H DOC #419, Accession no. M0365 (Box 178)
  - Index, Accession no. M0365 (Box 180)
  - Colorado River Hearings - briefs, notebooks, water resource items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 181)
  - Colorado River Hearings, Accession no. M0365 (Box 182)
  - Mineral Resource items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 183)
  - Mineral Resource items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 184)
  - Mineral Resource items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 185)
  - Referencebooks at Mr. Pietrowski's office, Accession no. M0365 (Box 186)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 187)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 189)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 190)
  - Mekong, Accession no. M0365 (Box 191)
  - Mekong, Accession no. M0365 (Box 192)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 193)
  - Water and Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 194)
  - Water and Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 195)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 196)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 197)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 198)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 199)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 200)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 201)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 202)
  - Arizona vs. California: unbound transcripts and misc. notes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 203)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 204)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 205)
  - Francis Wilson Hearings, misc. books, Accession no. M0365 (Box 206)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 207)
  - Francis Wilson Hearings, misc. books, Accession no. M0365 (Box 207)
  - Water Resource Items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 208)
  - Water Resource Items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 209)
  - Water Resources Items, Accession no. M0365 (Box 210)
  - Docket and minutes, Accession no. M0365 (Box 211)
  - Water, Power minerals, Accession no. M0365 (Box 212)
  - Water Rights cases S.Doc. #103, #149, Accession no. M0365 (Box 213)
  - Water Rights cases S.Doc. #103, #149, Accession no. M0365 (Box 214)
  - Colorado River Board (403 J04-S07), Accession no. M0365 (Box 215)
  - Colorado River Board (403 J04-S07), Accession no. M0365 (Box 216)
  - Colorado River Board (403 J04-S07), Accession no. M0365 (Box 217)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan Box 8 1604 F-1604T, Accession no. M0365 (Box 218)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan Box 8 1604 F-1604T, Accession no. M0365 (Box 219)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan Box 5 1602V 09-1602Z, Accession no. M0365 (Box 220)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan Box 5 1602V 09-1602Z, Accession no. M0365 (Box 221)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan Box 5 1602V 09-1602Z, Accession no. M0365 (Box 222)
  - Colorado River Board (A07-D), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 223)
  - Colorado River Board (A07-D), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 224)
  - Colorado River Board (A07-D), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 225)
  - Colorado River Board (U056-U14), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 226)
  - Colorado River Board (U056-U14), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 227)
  - Colorado River Board (U056-U14), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 228)
  - Arizona vs. California E-5-I 0154-APPA U-full clauses V-CWIP, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 229)
  - Arizona vs. California E-5-I 0154-APPA U-full clauses V-CWIP, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 230)
  - Arizona vs. California E-5-I 0154-APPA U-full clauses V-CWIP, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 231)
  - Colorado River drafts, etc. Compact Negotiations - confidential, Accession no. M0365 (Box 232)
  - Compact Negotiations - confidential, Accession no. M0365 (Box 233)
  - Colorado River Board - files, Accession no. M0365 (Box 234)
  - Colorado River Board - files, Accession no. M0365 (Box 235)
  - Colorado River Board - files, Accession no. M0365 (Box 236)
  - Colorado River Board - files, Accession no. M0365 (Box 237)
  - Colorado River Board - files, Accession no. M0365 (Box 238)
  - Colorado River Board (S08-U056) files, Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 239)
  - Colorado River Board (S08-U056) files, Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 240)
  - Colorado River Board (S08-U056) files, Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 241)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan (Box 3) 1602 KOZ-1602-RiO, Accession no. M0365 (Box 242)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan (Box 3) 1602 KOZ-1602-RiO, Accession no. M0365 (Box 243)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan (Box 3) 1602 KOZ-1602-RiO, Accession no. M0365 (Box 244)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 245)
  - Arizona vs. California pre-trial transcripts vol. 1-2, 3,6,42, 43, Accession no. M0365 (Box 246)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 247)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 248)
  - Vol. 14-20 reporters transcripts Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 249)
  - Vol. 21-27 Arizona vs. California reporters transcripts from trial, Accession no. M0365 (Box 250)
  - Boulder Canyon Project Act; A.I.M.E. Mineral Titles & Concessions Vol.11, Accession no. M0365 (Box 251)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1603 A01-1603 SOZ 6, Accession no. M0365 (Box 252)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1603 A01-1603 SOZ 6, Accession no. M0365 (Box 253)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1603 A01-1603 SOZ 6, Accession no. M0365 (Box 254)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 255)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 256)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365; 0180 (Box 257)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 258)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 259)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 260)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 261)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 262)
  - Arizona vs. California Docket, Accession no. M0365 (Box 263)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts vol. 28,29,31,32,33,34, Accession no. M0365 (Box 264)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts vol. 28,29,31,32,33,34, Accession no. M0365 (Box 265)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts vol. 28,29,31,32,33,34, Accession no. M0365 (Box 266)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts, Vol. 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, Accession no. M0365 (Box 267)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts, Vol. 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, Accession no. M0365 (Box 268)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts, Vol. 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, Accession no. M0365 (Box 269)
  - Arizona vs. California transcripts, Vol. 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, Accession no. M0365 (Box 270)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 271)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 272)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 273)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 274)
  - Water & Power Resources, Accession no. M0365 (Box 275)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 276)
  - Arizona vs. California, Accession no. M0365 (Box 277)
  - Colorado Basin Project Act 1968 Index H. Doc. #136, Accession no. M0365 (Box 278)
  - Colorado Basin Project Act 1968 Index H. Doc. #136, Accession no. M0365 (Box 279)
  - Colorado Basin Project Act 1968 Index H. Doc. #136, Accession no. M0365 (Box 280)
  - Colorado River Board (F01-J03), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 281)
  - Colorado River Board (F01-J03), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 282)
  - Colorado River Board (F01-J03), Accession no. M0365; 0345 (Box 283)
  - State of California, Accession no. M0365; 0303 (Box 284)
  - State of California, Accession no. M0365; 0303 (Box 285)
  - State of California, Accession no. M0365; 0303 (Box 286)
  - Colorado River Water Supply 9, Accession no. M0365; 0348 (Box 287)
  - Colorado River Water Supply 9, Accession no. M0365; 0348 (Box 288)
  - Colorado River Water Supply 9, Accession no. M0365; 0348 (Box 289)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1602-B08-1602 KOl2, Accession no. M0365 (Box 290)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1602-B08-1602 KOl2, Accession no. M0365 (Box 291)
  - Pacific Southwest Water Plan 1602-B08-1602 KOl2, Accession no. M0365 (Box 292)
  - Arizona vs. California Transcripts: Vol. 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 41, Accession no. M0365 (Box 293)
  - Arizona vs. California Transcripts: Vol. 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 41, Accession no. M0365 (Box 294)
  - Arizona vs. California Transcripts: Vol. 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 41, Accession no. M0365 (Box 295)
  - Small notebooks. "Master index by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 296)
  - Small notebooks. "Master index by Witness" & Newspaper clippings, notebooks, small notebooks- "Master Indexing by Witness", Accession no. M0365 (Box 297)